<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>LMC076h.护盾发生器（功能汉化版）</name>
	<targetVersion>1.0.2059</targetVersion>
	<author>JohnnyNova and Jetpack Maniac</author>
	<url>https://github.com/JonnyNova/Rimworld-Shields</url>
	<description>&lt;color=orange&gt;&lt;b&gt;汉化：jxb12306
Author jxb12306 FROM 3DM Localization Group
合集链接：http://bbs.3dmgame.com/thread-5842015-1-1.html
&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/color&gt;

警告：本汉化为基础功能版，未完成100%汉化，但是已经可以正常使用。
未汉化的部分：
-MOD配置
-内部菜单
-护盾崩溃事件提醒
NO ETA!!!

Allows for the building shield generators. Shields will stop projectiles that try to enter it but allow weapons to be fired out.  This includes bullets, rockets, mortar rounds, pods of **any** variety (enemies via drop pods, cargo pods, escape pods, and yes, **your** pods).  Shields have low idle power use and high power usage when stopping projectiles.  Shield strength is determined from stored battery power.  More batteries equals more protection.
允许建造护盾发生器。护盾将拦截试图来袭的远程火力，但允许武器从内部发射出去。这包括子弹、火箭、迫击炮、**任何**种类的吊舱（敌人通过吊舱、货舱、逃生舱，是的，**你的**舱）。护盾空闲时低功率使用，拦截时高功率使用。屏蔽强度由储存的蓄电池电力决定。更多的电力意味着更多的保护。


**Features:**
- Existing save compatible
- Stop projectiles (bullets, rockets, grenades, mortars, drop pods)
- Shields use a small amount of idle power
- Shield strength is the stored energy on your power net
- Shields generators will heat up as the shields absorb damage and will shut off if they overheat
- Shields come in three sizes:
- small (3m)
- medium (3m - 10m)
- large (5m - 25m)
- The small shield is minifiable and portable and contains an internal battery (1000 Wd, 50% efficient)
- Larger shields can soak more heat before the shield collapses
特性：
-存档兼容
-拦截远程火力
-空闲时低功耗
-护盾强度由储存的电力决定
-护盾发生器会持续升温并在过热时关闭
-护盾半径
-小（3米）
-中（3-10米）
-大（5-25米）
-便携式护盾发生器内置电池
-大型护盾发生器能吸收更多的伤害


**Shields Don't:**
- Stop movement of pawns in or out of the shields
- Stop fires
- Heal people
- Stop fires from explosions from propagating into the shield (Tip: don't stand near the edge if the bad guy has an incendiary launcher)
护盾不能做到
-阻止人们进出护盾
-熄灭火焰
-治疗人们
-阻止从外部蔓延进入护盾的火焰

**Compatibility:**
- No known mod conflicts

**Optionally Supported Mods:**
- Combat Extended (CE): Use the CE support expansion
- RedistHeat: Cool shields with ducts

Special Thanks to:

JohnnyNova: Code Lead
Jetpack Maniac: Code, documentation
Halno: Building and UI Art
Jaxxa: Inspired this mod from his ED-ShieldsBasic mod
Jdalt40: Update to b19

Version: 1.1.3.2096</description>
</ModMetaData>
